Wake up to reality!
!استيقظ على الحقيقة
Nothing ever goes as planned in this accursed world.
.لا شيء يسير كما هو مخطط له في هذا العالم الملعون
The longer you live, the more you realize
كلما عشت أكثر، كلما أدركت أكثر
that the only things that truly exist in this reality...
...أن الأشياء الوحيدة التي توجد فعلاً في هذه الحقيقة
are merely pain, suffering and futility.
.هي مجرد ألم ومعاناة وعبثية
Listen,
،استمع
everywhere you look in this world,
،أينما تنظر في هذا العالم
wherever there is light,
،حيثما يوجد ضوء
there will always be shadows to be found as well.
.سيكون هناك دائمًا ظلال يمكن العثور عليها أيضًا
As long as there is a concept of victors,
،طالما هناك مفهوم المنتصرين
the vanquished will also exist.
.فالمهزومون سيظلون موجودين أيضًا
The selfish intent of wanting to preserve peace,
،النية الأنانية في الرغبة في الحفاظ على السلام
initiates wars...
...تشعل الحروب
and hatred is born in order to protect love.
.ويولد الكراهية لحماية الحب
There are nexuses...
...هناك ترابطات
causal relationships that cannot be separated.
.علاقات سببية لا يمكن فصلها
I want to sever the fate of this world.
.أريد أن أقطع مصير هذا العالم
A world of only victors.
.عالم من المنتصرين فقط
A world of only peace.
.عالم من السلام فقط
A world of only love.
.عالم من الحب فقط
I will create such a world.
سأخلق مثل هذا العالم...
I am...
...أنا
the ghost of the Uchiha.
.شبح الأوتشيها
...
...
For truly this reality is a hell.
.لأن هذه الحقيقة جحيم حقًا
— Madara Uchiha A Legendary Villain from "Naruto" CC/Subtitle by Ahsan Habib Muaz
مادارا أوتشيها — شرير أسطوري من ناروتو الترجمة والتعليق بواسطة: أحسن حبيب معاذ